Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - P-S
        - Rush - Permanent waves, 1985; SR-27561; Rush (Box 65)
          Catalog # SRM 1-4001; A-side Matrix # HW SRM-1-4001-A-PRC-R-3-1-1
        - Rush, Bobby - Rush hour, 1979; SR-27562; Rush, Bobby (Box 65)
          Catalog # JZ 35509; A-side Matrix # P-I-R-AL-35509-1A F/WNS
        - Rush, Ed & Optical - Funktion; Naked lunch, 1998; SR-27563; Rush, Ed & Optical (Box 65)
          Catalog # V-026; A-side Matrix # V 026 A-1 STO
          V Recordings
        - Sa-Fire - Sa-Fire, 1988; SR-27564; Sa-Fire (Box 65)
          Catalog # 422 834 922-1; A-side Matrix # 422-834-922-1-AS-SP2 1-1
        - Sabota, Charles "Versatile" - Lethal club wax 4, 2001; SR-27565; Sabota, Charles "Versatile" (Box 65)
          Catalog # LCW-400; A-side Matrix # LCW-400 A1
          Lethal Club Wax
        - Sabu - Sabu, 1979; SR-27566; Sabu (Box 65)
          Catalog # SW-49902; A-side Matrix # S OR-49902 AS-1B
          Ocean Ariola America
        - Sabu - Sabu, 1980; SR-27567; Sabu (Box 65)
          Catalog # MCA-3236; A-side Matrix # 'EDDY'' MCA 2176 W1
        - Sacco, Lou Christie - Paint America love, 1971; SR-27568; Sacco, Lou Christie (Box 65)
          Catalog # BDS 5073; A-side Matrix # BDS 5073-A-2 SON
          Buddah Records
        - Sade - The best of Sade (disc one), 1994; SR-27569; Sade (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27570. Double album.
          Catalog # 477793 1; A-side Matrix # 01-477793-20-4A-1
        - Sade - The best of Sade (disc two), 1994; SR-27570; Sade (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27569. Double album.
          Catalog # 477793 1; A-side Matrix # 01-477793-20-3C-1
        - Sages Poetes De La Rue - Qu'est-ce qui fait marcher les Sages (disc one), 1995; SR-27571; Sages Poetes De La Rue (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27572. Double album.
          Catalog # 121102; A-side Matrix # MPO 121102 A LES SAGES POETES SIDE A
          Wotre Music
        - Sages Poetes De La Rue - Qu'est-ce qui fait marcher les Sages (disc two), 1995; SR-27572; Sages Poetes De La Rue (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27571. Double album.
          Catalog # 121102; A-side Matrix # MPO LES SAGES POETES SIDE C 121102 C
        - Saïan Supa Crew - Saïan Supa Crew (KLR), 1999; SR-27573; Saïan Supa Crew (Box 65)
          Catalog # VISA 8398; A-side Matrix # VISA 8398 A JZ
          Source
        - St. Kenerly, Roger - Gotta keep on dancin', 1979; SR-27574; St. Kenerly, Roger; Spruill, Stephanie (Box 65)
          Catalog # CRP-703; A-side Matrix # T1 CP 703-SA-2 CTH
        - St. Kenerly, Roger - Saint & Stephanie, 1979; SR-27584; St. Kenerly, Roger; Spruill, Stephanie (Box 65)
          Catalog # AB 4233; A-side Matrix # T1 AB-4233-SA RE-1-A-CTH
        - Saint-Prix, Dédé - Lerdou, 1987; SR-27585; Saint-Prix, Dédé (Box 65)
          Catalog # 8232; A-side Matrix # 8232 A AM
          Blue Silver
        - Saint Tropez - Hot and nasty, 1982; SR-27575; Saint Tropez (Box 65)
          Catalog # DLA-10004; A-side Matrix # DLA-10004-A PRCC
          Destiny Records
        - Salsoul Orchestra - How high, 1978; SR-27576; Salsoul Orchestra (Box 65)
          Catalog # SA 8528; A-side Matrix # N SA-8528-A JR
        - Salt 'N' Pepa - Hot cool vicious, 1986; SR-27577; Salt 'N' Pepa (Box 65)
          Catalog # PL1007; A-side Matrix # PL-1007-A 1-1
          Next Plateau Records Inc.
        - Salt 'N' Pepa - Very necessary, 1993; SR-27578; Salt 'N' Pepa (Box 65)
          Catalog # 828454-1; A-side Matrix # 828454-1-A
          FFRR
        - Salt 'N' Pepa - Expression, 1992; SR-27579; Salt 'N' Pepa (Box 65)
          Catalog # FXDJ 182; A-side Matrix # FXDJ-182-A1
        - Salt 'N' Pepa - Expression (the Brixton bass mix), 1990; SR-27586; Salt 'N' Pepa (Box 65)
          Catalog # FXDJ 127; A-side Matrix # MT FXDJ-127-A1
        - Sam & The Soul Machine - Po'k bones & rice, 2002; SR-27580; Sam & The Soul Machine (Box 65)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0039; A-side Matrix # DEL LP 0039 A MCR
          Funky Delicacies
        - Sam The Beast - Lockdown, 1996; SR-27581; Sam The Beast (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27582. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CLR 7211; A-side Matrix # CLR-7211-A-RE F/WRCE
          CLR
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - Sam The Beast - Lockdown, 1996; SR-27582; Sam The Beast (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27581. 2 copies.
        - Sampa Crew - Super remixes, 1992; SR-27583; Sampa Crew (Box 65)
          Catalog # RQN031; A-side Matrix # BMG RQN031-A ISTA 1
          Kaskata's Records
          São Paulo, Brazil
        - Sandpebbles of Barbados - Enjoy yourself, 1973; SR-27587; Sandpebbles of Barbados (Box 65)
          Catalog # PG-1010; A-side Matrix # PGR-1010-S1
          Island Series
        - Sá, Sandra de - Vale tudo, 1983; SR-27588; Sá, Sandra de; de Sá, Sandra (Box 65)
          Catalog # 303.6018; A-side Matrix # RCA 303-6018-A IS A 1
          RGE
        - Sands, Evie - Keep my lovelight burnin', 1979; SR-27589; Sands, Evie (Box 65)
          Catalog # JT-11549; A-side Matrix # PD-11549-A-1S
        - Sans Pression - 514-50 Dans mon réseau (disc one), 1999; SR-27590; Sans Pression (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27591. Double album.
          Catalog # MRLVL-5069; A-side Matrix # 514-50-A-1 CUT BY ''THE INHABITANT''
          Les Disques MONT REAL Inc.
          Montreal, Canada
        - Sans Pression - 514-50 Dans mon réseau (disc two), 1999; SR-27591; Sans Pression (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27590. Double album.
          Catalog # MRLVL-5069; A-side Matrix # 514-50-C-1 CUT BY ''THE INHABITANT''
        - Santamaria, Mongo - Mongo Santamaria's greatest hits, 1970; SR-27592; Santamaria, Mongo (Box 65)
          Catalog # CS 1060; A-side Matrix # XSM153215-1D
        - Santamaria, Mongo - Mongo Santamaria's greatest hits, 1970; SR-27593; Santamaria, Mongo (Box 65)
        - Santamaria, Mongo - Live at Yankee Stadium, 1974; SR-27594; Santamaria, Mongo (Box 65)
          Catalog # XVS-26; A-side Matrix # X VS-26-A SON
          Vaya Records
        - Santana - One chain (Don't make no prison), 1978; SR-27595; Santana (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27596. Different discs.
          Catalog # 23-10957; A-side Matrix # XSS-165796-1C
        - Santana - One chain (Don't make no prison), 1978; SR-27596; Santana (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27595. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS 585; A-side Matrix # XSM-165749-1H TML-S
        - Satisfaction Unlimited - Think of the children, 1972; SR-27597; Satisfaction Unlimited (Box 65)
          Catalog # HA-716; A-side Matrix # HA716A-RAD SON K-5768
          Hot Wax
        - Saturday Night Band - Come on dance, dance, 1978; SR-27598; Saturday Night Band (Box 65)
          Catalog # PRL 12155; A-side Matrix # PRELUDE PRL-12155-AS-RE CP2 F/W S
        - Sayer, Leo - Endless flight, 1976; SR-27599; Sayer, Leo (Box 65)
          Catalog # BS 2962; A-side Matrix # BS-1-2962-RE-1 LW-1 AZ
        - Scandal - I wanna do it, 1981; SR-27600; Scandal; Genesis, Lee (Box 65)
          Catalog # S-12338; A-side Matrix # S 12338-1-2A
        - Schoener, Eberhard - Video-magic, 1981; SR-27601; Schoener, Eberhard (Box 65)
          Catalog # ST-12171; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12171-G2
          Harvest
        - Schoolly D - Smoke some kill, 1988; SR-27602; Schoolly D (Box 65)
          Catalog # 1118-1-JDAB; A-side Matrix # 1118-1-JD-A-10F/W
          Jive
        - Schönheitsfehler - Sex, drugs and Hip Hop (disc one), 2000; SR-27603; Schönheitsfehler (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27604. Double album.
          Catalog # 561 657-1; A-side Matrix # 561 657-1 A DMM HP
          Motor Music
        - Schönheitsfehler - Sex, drugs and Hip Hop (disc two), 2000; SR-27604; Schönheitsfehler (Box 65)
          In same jacket as # SR-27603. Double album.
          Catalog # 561 657-1; A-side Matrix # 561 657-1 C DMM HP
        - Scientists Of Sound - 1.4.4. or bust (the replenishing) (disc one), 1996; SR-27605; Scientists Of Sound (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27606. Double album.
          Catalog # DLLP2; A-side Matrix # DOWNLOW-SOS-001-A DLLP 2 A1 PR-CCO
          Downlow Entertainment
        - Scientists Of Sound - 1.4.4. or bust (the replenishing) (disc two), 1996; SR-27606; Scientists Of Sound (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27605. Double album.
          Catalog # DLLP2; A-side Matrix # DOWNLOW-SOS-001-C DLLP 2 C2 PR-CCO
        - Scott, Millie - Love me right, 1987; SR-27607; Scott, Millie (Box 66)
          Catalog # BRLP 511; A-side Matrix # BWIX TA1BB BRLP 511 A-1U-1-1-X1
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - Reflections, 1981; SR-27608; Scott-Heron, Gil (Box 66)
          Catalog # AL 9566; A-side Matrix # AL 9566-SA-X
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - Midnight band: the first minute of a new day, 1975; SR-27609; Scott-Heron, Gil; Jackson, Brian (Box 66)
          Catalog # A 4030; A-side Matrix # ARS 4030-S-A AL F/W NYC
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - 1980, 1980; SR-27610; Scott-Heron, Gil; Jackson, Brian (Box 66)
          Catalog # AL 9514; A-side Matrix # S AL-9514-SA SMI SX
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - Small talk at 125th and Lenox, 1970; SR-27611; Scott-Heron, Gil (Box 66)
          Catalog # FDS-131; A-side Matrix # 3972-FDS 10131-1 (A) S-44526 DRB65
          Flying Dutchman
        - Scott-Heron, Gil - Re-ron, 1984; SR-27612; Scott-Heron, Gil (Box 66)
          Catalog # ADP-9216; A-side Matrix # ADP-9216-SA-1- MUB
        - Scratch D vs. H Bomb - The red pill, 2001; SR-27613; Scratch D vs. H Bomb (Box 66)
          Catalog # FM006; A-side Matrix # FM-006-A GUY'S THE EXCHANGE
          Freakin' Music
          West Palm Beach, Florida
        - Scratchy Muffin - Got beef E.P., 1996; SR-27614; Scratchy Muffin (Box 66)
          Catalog # SKINT 18; A-side Matrix # WHITEHAWKS UP BUT KEMPTOWNS NEVER DOWN! SKINT 18 A1 SIMON-THE EXCHANGE
          Skint
        - Screechie Don - New dance; Show dem how to boogle; Can't dance, 1992; SR-27615; Screechie Don; Ranks, Sluggy; Metro, Peter; Culture, Birdie (Box 66)
          Catalog # DM-007; A-side Matrix # DM 007-A BOGLE DANCE PAUL-UP
          Diamond Music
        - Scrunter - Party lover, 1988; SR-27616; Scrunter (Box 66)
          Catalog # J.N.-001; A-side Matrix # JN-001-A HERBIE JR
          TCA Records
          Staten Island, New York
        - Scrunter - Every shadow, 1985; SR-27617; Scrunter (Box 66)
          Catalog # SCR 372; A-side Matrix # SCP-372-A
        - Sea Level - Sneakers fifty four, 1978; SR-27618; Sea Level (Box 66)
          Catalog # CPD-0001; A-side Matrix # AS-CPD-0001 XX
          Macon, Georgia
        - Search - Peanut butter and jam; Missing you, 1982; SR-27619; Search; Turner, Buddy; Conway, T.G. (Box 66)
          Catalog # PWR-2005; A-side Matrix # PWR-2005-A HERBIE JR SMK
          Philly World Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Second Image - Fall in love, 1982; SR-27620; Second Image (Box 66)
          Catalog # PD D 522; A-side Matrix # PDD 52282 NP 5955 PRC C 1-1-1 -A-
        - Secret Weapon - Secret Weapon, 1983; SR-27621; Secret Weapon (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27622. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRL 14107 AS; A-side Matrix # PRL-14107-AS SG FW
        - Secret Weapon - Secret Weapon, 1983; SR-27622; Secret Weapon (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27621. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRL 14107 AS; A-side Matrix # A-1 PRL-14107-AS SG FW
        - Sens Unik - Chromatic (disc one), 1994; SR-27623; Sens Unik (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27624. Double album.
          Catalog # UR 8 LP; A-side Matrix # SNA 94-5 UR 8 LP A1
          Unik Records
          Lausanne, Switzerland
        - Sens Unik - Chromatic (disc two), 1994; SR-27624; Sens Unik (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27623. Double album.
          Catalog # UR 8 LP; A-side Matrix # SNA 94-5 UR 8 LP C1
        - Sequence - The Sequence, 1982; SR-27625; Sequence (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27626. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SH-267; A-side Matrix # VID-324-A
          Sugar Hill Records
        - Sequence - The Sequence, 1982; SR-27626; Sequence (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27625. 2 copies.
        - Sequence - The sequence party, 1983; SR-27627; Sequence (Box 66)
          Catalog # SH-9200; A-side Matrix # VID-330-A TRUTONE-pa 12-83
        - Sevelle, Taja - Taja Sevelle, 1987; SR-27628; Sevelle, Taja (Box 66)
          Catalog # 1-25546; A-side Matrix # 1-255461-25546-A-SH5 B-28205-SH5 SB 17275 1-1
          Paisley Park
        - Severed Heads - Stretcher, 1985; SR-27629; Severed Heads (Box 66)
          Catalog # INK 1214; A-side Matrix # MPO INK 1214 A2 A FORKY PRIME VT
          Ink Records
        - Sex Kraz'd Superstars - Feelin' horney, 1996; SR-27630; Sex Kraz'd Superstars (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27631. 2 copies.
          Catalog # UC 207; A-side Matrix # UC 207-A MMM JR
          Underground Construction
          Schiller Park, Illinois
        - Sex Kraz'd Superstars - Feelin' horney, 1996; SR-27631; Sex Kraz'd Superstars (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27630. 2 copies.
        - Sgt. Rock - We're in heaven EP, 2000; SR-27632; Sgt. Rock (Box 66)
          Catalog # WIJ 119T; A-side Matrix # GUY'S THE EXCHANGE WIJ 119T A1
          Wiiija Records
        - Sgt. Rock - His first full bout Supadickie, 1999; SR-27933; Sgt. Rock (Box 66)
          Catalog # WIJ 105 T; A-side Matrix # WIT 105 T A2 DAMONT
        - Shadow - Sweet sweet dreams, 1984; SR-27633; Shadow; Mighty Shadow (Box 66)
          Catalog # WB-0048; A-side Matrix # WB-48-A
          Kalico Records
        - Shadow - Love lite, 1979; SR-27634; Shadow; Mighty Shadow (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27635. Different discs.
          Catalog # 6E-233; A-side Matrix # 6E-233 A Re SP
        - Shadow - I need love, 1979; SR-27635; Shadow; Mighty Shadow (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27634. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS-11431; A-side Matrix # AS-11431 A-SP 1-2
        - Shadow - High tension, 1988; SR-27636; Shadow; Mighty Shadow (Box 66)
          Catalog # GS2279; A-side Matrix # K GS 2279-A
        - Shadow - Better than ever, 1986; SR-27637; Shadow; Mighty Shadow (Box 66)
          Catalog # SCR 371; A-side Matrix # SCR 371 A F/W
        - Shadow - Return of de bassman, 1984; SR-27638; Shadow; Mighty Shadow (Box 66)
          Catalog # GS-2251; A-side Matrix # SR-009A FW C5
        - 2Pac - R U still down? [Remember me] (Disc one), 1997; SR-28813; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28814; SR-28815. Triple album.
          Catalog # 01241-41628-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-41628+1A 1
        - 2Pac - R U still down? [Remember me] (Disc two), 1997; SR-28814; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28813; SR-28815. Triple album.
          Catalog # 01241-41628-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-41628+2A 1
        - 2Pac - R U still down? [Remember me] (Disc three), 1997; SR-28815; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28813; SR-28814. Triple album.
          Catalog # 01241-41628-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-41628+3A 1
        - 2Pac - Live (Disc one), 2004; SR-28816; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac; Knight, Suge (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28817. Double album.
          Catalog # KOC-LP-5746; A-side Matrix # KOC-LP-5746-A
          Koch Records
        - 2Pac - Live (Disc two), 2004; SR-28817; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac; Knight, Suge (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28816. Double album.
          Catalog # KOC-LP-5746; A-side Matrix # KOC-LP-5746-C
        - 2Pac - Better dayz (Disc one), 2002; SR-28818; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac; Knight, Suge; Shakur, Afeni (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28819; SR-28820; SR-28821. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # 694970711; A-side Matrix # 06949-7071-1A
          Interscope Records
        - 2Pac - Better dayz (Disc two), 2002; SR-28819; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac; Knight, Suge; Shakur, Afeni (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28818; SR-28820; SR-28821. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # 694970711; A-side Matrix # 06949-7072-1A
        - 2Pac - Better dayz (Disc three), 2002; SR-28820; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac; Knight, Suge; Shakur, Afeni (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28818; SR-28819; SR-28821. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # 694970711; A-side Matrix # 0044-50255-1A
        - 2Pac - Better dayz (Disc four), 2002; SR-28821; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac; Knight, Suge; Shakur, Afeni (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28818; SR-28819; SR-28820. Quadruple album.
          Catalog # 694970711; A-side Matrix # 0044-50256-1A
        - 2Pac - Me against the world (Disc one), 1995; SR-28822; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28823. Double album.
          Catalog # 92399-1; A-side Matrix # STIN-959951 A F/W RCE
        - 2Pac - Me against the world (Disc two), 1995; SR-28823; 2Pac; Shakur, Tupac (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-28822. Double album.
          Catalog # 92399-1; A-side Matrix # STIN-959953-A F/W RCE
        - 2Pac - Lost souls; These days, 1997; SR-28824; 2Pac; Skakur, Tupac; Outlawz; Nate Dogg; Dillinger, Daz (Box 66)
          Catalog # SPRO 30230; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30230-RE1 SIDE A S-3LP03
          Death Row Records
        - Shalamar - Circumstantial evidence, 1987; SR-27639; Shalamar (Box 66)
          Catalog # ST-72556; A-side Matrix # AL-SP ST-1-72556 F-2 13-27844-F2 16919 SP 0-1
          Solar
        - Shalamar - Uptown festival, 1977; SR-27640; Shalamar (Box 66)
          Catalog # SD-10906; A-side Matrix # SD-10906 A 5S
          Soul Train
        - Shalamar - Friends, 1982; SR-27658; Shalamar (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27659. Different discs.
          Catalog # S-28; A-side Matrix # SP 0-1/SM2-1 S-28-A- 1SH-SP+SLM+ 09 Wavy
        - Shalamar - A night to remember, 1982; SR-27659; Shalamar (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27658. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS-11553; A-side Matrix # AM-H553-A 1SP Wavy
        - Shalamar - The second time around, 1979; SR-27660; Shalamar (Box 66)
          Catalog # JD-11733; A-side Matrix # K-11195 YD-11733-A 2S Wavy
        - Shannon - Do you wanna get away, 1985; SR-27641; Shannon (Box 66)
          Catalog # 90267-1; A-side Matrix # SSTWTG-855653-B HERBIE JR
          Mirage
        - Shanté - Big mama, 1992; SR-27642; Shanté (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27643. 2 copies.
          Catalog # LL 102; A-side Matrix # CSB FF LL-0-102 A
          Livin' Large Records
        - Shanté - Big mama, 1992; SR-27643; Shanté (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27642. 2 copies.
        - Shanté, Roxanne - Def mix vol.1, 1985; SR-27644; Shanté, Roxanne (Box 66)
          Catalog # PA-4450; A-side Matrix # PA-4450-A
          Pop Art Records
        - Sharam - (Keep on) move it, 1996; SR-27645; Sharam (Box 66)
          Catalog # 12SENSE4; A-side Matrix # 12SENSE4 A
          Low Sense
        - Shazz - Shazz (disc one), 1998; SR-27646; Shazz (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27647. Double album.
          Catalog # 14-489973-20; A-side Matrix # 14 489973 20 /A GOP-TR
        - Shazz - Shazz (disc two), 1998; SR-27647; Shazz (Box 66)
          In same jacket as # SR-27646. Double album.
          Catalog # 14-489973-20; A-side Matrix # GOP-TR- 14 489973 20 / C1
        - Shazzy - Keep it flowin', 1990; SR-27648; Shazzy (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27649. 2 copies.
          Catalog # ED 5417; A-side Matrix # DMS HERBIE JR SP1-1 ST-ED-66666 A DMM-1
        - Shazzy - Keep it flowin', 1990; SR-27649; Shazzy (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27648. 2 copies.
        - She Rockers - Jam it jam, 1990; SR-27650; She Rockers (Box 67)
          Catalog # PROMO 26; A-side Matrix # 89 9 PR MO 26 A1 MILES
        - Sheena & the Rokkets - Sheena & the Rokkets, 1981; SR-27651; Sheena & the Rokkets (Box 67)
          Catalog # SP-4875; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 04875-A-P2
        - Sheila and B. Devotion - Sheila and B. Devotion, 1980; SR-27652; Sheila and B. Devotion (Box 67)
          Catalog # CAR 38-124; A-side Matrix # 0-1 ST-CAR-804479-E S-P
        - Sheila and B. Devotion - Spacer, 1979; SR-27653; Sheila and B. Devotion (Box 67)
          Catalog # DSKO 213; A-side Matrix # ST-DK-37605-5
        - Sheila E. - Sheila E, 1997; SR-27654; Sheila E. (Box 67)
          Catalog # 925 498-1; A-side Matrix # 1-2 14889 12 GER 1-25498-A-SH1 B-25941-SH1 R/S Alsdorf 925498-1-A
        - Sheila E. - Shelia E, 1997; SR-27655; Sheila E. (Box 67)
          Catalog # 925 498-1; A-side Matrix # 1-2 14889 GER 1-25498-A-SH1 B-25941-SH1 71 R/S Alsodorf 925498-1-A
        - Sheila E. - In the glamorous life, 1984; SR-27656; Sheila E. (Box 67)
          Catalog # 1-25107; A-side Matrix # 1-25107-A-SH1 B-19228-SH1 SLM 6489 1-1
        - Sheila E. - In romance 1600, 1985; SR-27657; Sheila E. (Box 67)
          Catalog # 1-25317; A-side Matrix # 1-25317-A-SR4
        - Sheridan, Ann C. - Sing it low, 1979; SR-27661; Sheridan, Ann C. (Box 67)
          Catalog # JD-11049; A-side Matrix # D PD-11049 A-2
        - Shinehead - Rough & rugged, 1986; SR-27662; Shinehead (Box 67)
          Catalog # ALMPL 001; A-side Matrix # ALMLP-001-A SHINEHEAD LP
          African Love Records
        - Shock - Shock, 1981; SR-27664; Shock (Box 67)
          Catalog # F-9613; A-side Matrix # F 9613 A S-2 SX
        - Shock - Nite life, 1983; SR-27665; Shock (Box 67)
          Catalog # F-9622; A-side Matrix # P F 9622 A
        - Shock - Let your body do the talkin', 1981; SR-27666; Shock (Box 67)
          Catalog # D-203; A-side Matrix # D-203 A 1 S SX
        - Short, Bobby - The mad twenties, 1974; SR-27667; Short, Bobby (Box 67)
          Catalog # SD 1664; A-side Matrix # ST-A 743193-A PR
        - Shot In The Dark - Shot In The Dark, 1981; SR-27668; Shot In The Dark (Box 67)
          Catalog # RS-1-3096; A-side Matrix # T RS 13096-AS CT 2
        - Shotgun - Shotgun IV, 1980; SR-27669; Shotgun (Box 67)
          Catalog # MCA-3201; A-side Matrix # MCA 2053 KR1 JMS
        - Shotgun - Kingdom come, 1980; SR-27670; Shotgun (Box 67)
          Catalog # MCA-5137; A-side Matrix # MCA-2342-AM-1
        - Showbiz & A.G. - Fat pockets, 1992; SR-27671; Showbiz & A.G. (Box 67)
          Catalog # 869 931-1; A-side Matrix # TD 422-8-869-931-1-A
          Payday
        - Shrapnel - Shrapnel, 1984; SR-27672; Shrapnel (Box 67)
          Catalog # 60281-1; A-side Matrix # H1 SUDSY STE-60281A-2B
        - Shriekback - Lined up; My spine, 1983; SR-27673; Shriekback (Box 67)
          Catalog # YT 106; A-side Matrix # 020 A-8204 B-1 BUNDA TAIME
          Y Records
        - Shy FX - The message; Nasty, 1996; SR-27674; Shy FX (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27675. 2 copies.
          Catalog # EBR 008; A-side Matrix # EBR 008-A -JTS-
          Ebony Recordings
        - Shy FX - The message; Nasty, 1996; SR-27675; Shy FX (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27674. 2 copies.
        - Siaule - Illegal ghetto mix vol. 3, 1999; SR-27676; Siaule (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27677. 2 copies.
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # ACT IS DFI 01-L LA SIAULE 03 A
        - Siaule - Illegal ghetto mix vol. 3, 1999; SR-27677; Siaule (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27676. 2 copies.
        - Sichran, Bobby - From a sympathetical hurricane, 1994; SR-27678; Sichran, Bobby (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27679. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CAS 6246; A-side Matrix # XSS-6246-A-1B
        - Sichran, Bobby - From a sympathetical hurricane, 1994; SR-27679; Sichran, Bobby (Box 67)
          In same jacket as # SR-27678. 2 copies.